UNITE Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements 6000/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements
1995- 1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/008
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes files of the International Ladies Garment Workers Union and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union from both the Research Department and the Operations Department.
6766327
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Collective bargaining, Clothing industry, New York (State), New York; Collective bargaining, Textile industry, New York (State), New York; Textile workers, Labor unions, New York (State), New York; Clothing workers, Labor unions, New York (State), New York; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees.; Accurate Lace Dye Experts, Inc., Archives; Ajax Shoulder Pad Company, Inc., Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Archives; American White Cross, Inc., Archives; Bari Manufacturing Corporation, Archives; Biener and Son, Inc., Archives; Brooks Brothers (Firm), Archives; Buster Brown Apparel, Inc., Archives; California Ranchwear, Archives; Chase Packaging Corporation, Archives; Cleve-Tenn Industries, Inc., Archives; Cliftex Corporation/Cutting Room, Archives; College House Manufacturing, Archives; Columbia Wool Scouring Mills, Archives; Cone Mills Corporation, Archives; Cooper Sportswear Manufacturing Company, Inc., Archives; Country Miss, Inc., Archives; Crown Yarn Dye Company, Inc., Archives; Hallmark Emblems, Inc., Archives; Harris-Tipograph, Inc., Archives; Ideal Shoulder Pad Company, Archives; Imperial Coat Front Company, Inc., Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Archives; Interstate Dyeing and Finishing Company, Archives; Kellwood Company, Archives; Lee County Manufacturing, Archives; Lehigh Valley Throwing Mills, Inc., Archives; Levi Strauss and Company, Archives; Lilly Industrial Coatings, Archives; Meren Industries, Inc., Archives; Mespo Umbrella Ltd., Archives; Midlantic/New York Pad, Archives; Miller Brothers, Inc., Archives; Missbrenner Prints, Inc., Archives; Moderne Gloves, Inc., Archives; Monroe Prints, Inc., Archives; Montreal Fast Print, Ltd., Archives; National Knitted Processors, Inc., Archives; Oneita Industries, Inc., Archives; Peerless Rug Ltd., Archives; Perennial Print Corporation, Archives; Perfection Pad Company, Inc., Archives; Poughkeepsie Finishing Corporation, Archives; Rainbow Dyeing and Finishing Company, Archives; River Warping, Inc., Archives; Schertz Umbrellas, Inc., Archives; Sierra Plastics, Inc., Archives; Societe de la Broderie, Archives; Tavernon Photo Engraving Company, Archives; Techniplast, Inc., Archives; Texas Apparel, Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, Archives.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Operations Department.; UNITE HERE (Organization), Archives; United Global Distributors, Inc., Archives; Warwick Dying Corporation, Archives; Wimpfheimer A. and Brothers, Inc., Archives; Windsor Textile Processing, Inc., Archives
6766327
- AJAX, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Altoona Mattress Mfg. Co., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Amoco Fabrics & Fibers LTD, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Blue Surf of Canada LTD Oshawa, On, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bullock & Jones San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Charell LTD Montreal, PQ, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cliftex Corp/Cutting Room, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Consolidated Contractors Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Corbin LTD, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cortese Inc., 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Illinois Glove Co., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Illinois Glove Co., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Irwin Mfg. Co. Ltd., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Besner, J.A. & Sons Ltd., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Briggs, Jay Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Koret of California Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lehigh Valley Throwing Mills Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lilly Industries Inc., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- L C Footwear LLC, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Malden Mills Industries Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Miller Brothers Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Missbrenner, Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- National Knitted Processors Inc., 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Oneita Industries Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Phoenix Dye Works, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Poughkeepsie Finishing Corp, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Prima Warping Inc., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Products Arc-Fil LTEE (LES), 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Rossmor Industries, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- S.R. Gent (Canada) Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Salomon, L. & Sons, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Strauss, Levi & Co, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Strauss, Levi & Co, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Scranton Export Clothing Co. Inc., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- T.M.S. Multimedia Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Techniplast Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- United Global Distributors Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Wimpfheimer A. & Bro. Inc., 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Windsor Textile Processing Inc., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)